My lady,
this is our chance！
That idiot Livia just called
off the wedding with the Godfather!
What?!
They think he is
just some ordinary miner.
Livia publicly broke the engagement and
married his pathetic little brother instead!
Oh, thank the
gods for stupid women!
Send word immediately.
Prepare the most extravagant gift.
I’m going to propose
to the Godfather myself.
Move!
Blade!
You’re here!
Who the hell hit you?
Step forward right now!
It was him.
You’re the one who hit Redmond?
Get out now, or you’re next.
What did you just say?
You’re gonna hit me?
You guys hear that?
This punk says
he’s gonna hit me.
Who the hell is this guy?
So freaking bold?
He’s the disowned
trash of House Carter.
Spends all day
banging rocks with a
bunch of lowborns in the mines.
Just a miner, huh?
No wonder you don’t
know who I am.
Listen up, I'm the Blade.
See this blood on my blade?
That’s what I do.
Lord Severin, I’ve heard enough.